The Witch of the Forbidden Forest?
Is that even possible?
Not with magic.
However, there's an artifact
that makes it possible.
You mean one of the outsiders'
artifacts that Travis mentioned?
I see.
It seems you have memories
from before history was changed.
The demon king told you all of that?
The nerve of him...
Why are you after Eleterria?
What other reason could there be?
I want to change the past.
Then wouldn't one be enough?
It would be meaningless without both of them.
Shouldn't you go ahead
and make your way to her instead?
She doesn't want my help.
Do you really believe that
after all you've been through?
You may have exerted no effort
to win her over this time around,
but that's no excuse to be lazy.
You always suffer a great deal
each time to make her fall for you.
It's not often she loves you
from the beginning.
So do take some initiative.
Perhaps for you, other women
could take her place.
But for her, you're the only one she has.
What are you talking about?
How presumptuous of you,
like you've seen it all.
That I have.
There was once a time when
I served under the two of you.
What?
Please, do be on your way.
Right now, Tuldarr... she's the one
who's taken on the task,
but aren't you the one who
should be confronting the witch?
You said she's not irreplaceable to me?
It's the truth.
Who cares about the times
I have no memories of?
She's the only one for me.
And I'm about to prove it.
Well, we'll see about that...
~ At Memory's End ~
Tuldarr Army
Magdalsia Army
There they are!
Magdalsian troops!
Soldiers of Tuldarr.
You have nothing to fear.
I promise we will reign victorious.
No matter who stands in our way,
they will never intrude upon our nation.
Charge!
Onward!
You think the mere queen of Tuldarr
stands any chance against a witch?
I'll beat that arrogance out of you.
Who's the arrogant one here?
If it's me you're after,
pay the price with your life.
Would you happen to know where Senn's gone?
Senn?
My spirit.
Aren't you the Witch of the Forbidden Forest?
That's right.
I am that very witch.
Senn knew all about you.
Isn't that why you captured him?
So he wouldn't reveal your identity to me?
Where is he now?
Why, I couldn't say.
Then we have nothing more to discuss.
This is where you die.
Tinasha.
What are you doing here, Oscar?!
Just listen for now.
It's not the witch residing in that body.
Inside is the mind of Magdalsia's king.
What?
The real witch's soul is trapped
inside the Mirror of Oblivion.
Same goes for that spirit of yours.
The Mirror of Oblivion is apparently
an outsiders' artifact
that traps people's minds
and memories to record them.
And who told you this?
Valt.
What?!
You're right to be skeptical.
But I want you to head to
Magdalsia and destroy the mirror.
That should turn the witch back to normal.
If you can't find the mirror,
you can simply teleport back here.
I'll take care of the one up there.
What?
This is Tuldarr's war to fight.
It's unthinkable to have
a bystander like you take part!
I appreciate the information,
but please head back to Farsas.
No, thanks.
I'm going to get mad.
I am not your wife.
I am queen of Tuldarr.
I cannot allow you to intervene.
The battle's mostly over already.
All that's left is you against the witch
and the cleanup.
I'm saying I can finish this
in a way that'll satisfy you.
My satisfaction shouldn't come
at the cost of breaking the status quo.
A ruler is but a cog to ensure
that a country runs smoothly.
I mustn't let my own emotions
get in the way of that.
That's right. You mustn't.
There's no one who can act in your place.
Four hundred years ago, you made it all alone.
There's nothing anyone else can share with you.
Hesitation breeds weakness.
So I mustn't falter, now of all times.
I can even forget... that which I hold dear.
I understand your side as well.
But things have changed since back then.
Don't bear all the burden alone.
Rely on me so you don't regret it later.
If you do, I'll share your burden
for the rest of my life.
Believe in me.
I can't do that.
Let's say you hold the fort here,
and I break the mirror.
What will you do if the real witch tries to
kill you after returning to her own body?!
If that happens, I'll kill the witch.
That's what this sword is for.
I command all spirits who can hear me.
I have two commands for you.
The first is don't be killed.
The second is to temporarily recognize
the wielder of Akashia as your master
and lend him your support.
Crybaby.
Quiet, you.
The king of Farsas...
The one who wields Akashia!
Don't disappoint me and die here.
We haven't even gotten married yet.
I couldn't die with regrets like that.
He'll be here to keep you busy.
I'll be seeing you later.
How dare you.
It's no fun tormenting a man.
Don't talk big with those borrowed powers.
I already know you're nothing but an impostor.
You little whelp...
We'll see how true that is once
I've torn you to shreds.
Without a care in the world.
There it is.
Senn, can you hear me?
My queen!
That's him!
My queen! You're here!
Senn!
What a relief...
Um, is that the witch?
Yes, that's the Witch of the Forbidden Forest.
You must really care for her.
Well...
You could say she's a handful.
Oh?
What are you doing here?
I came looking for Senn.
That would mean you're Tuldarr's queen.
Your astonishing magic levels
made me think you were a new witch.
So? What is it you want?
I was hoping to break this mirror.
Are you the Witch of the Forbidden Forest?
I am.
You can call me Lucrezia.
Oh, right, you wouldn't use my name anyway.
I will.
This pillar has created
a conceptual tear in the mirror.
So punching another hole from
the outside might be able to break it.
Hm?
Well, if it can be broken,
then please go ahead.
What must be defined is power.
The ocean of life.
Wills meld together in the past.
A spiral geyser piercing
the earth from the skies.
Six doors locked shut.
Voices of premonition.
I command the end of twilight.
I can't let him down...
I can't fail here...
I will overcome this!
I believe!
Huh, she's pretty good.
Yeah.
You'd be a powerless brat without that sword.
Do you not fear this witch?!
I'd rather not hear that from you.
Also, witches are a lot scarier.
I'm left wanting with you in her body.
Come again?
Wait...
It can't be...
No...
No!
It's been so long since I've had fresh air.
Good evening.
Are you Lucrezia?
Indeed I am.
Wait, don't tell me you're
the Akashia swordsman?
You have an awful lot of magic if so.
You're no mage, are you?
I am the Akashia swordsman.
I have magic as Lavinia's grandson.
Lavinia did what?!
With the Farsas royal bloodline?!
I can hardly believe it!
Where's Tinasha?
She's still with Senn.
I imagine she'll come back before long.
I see.
What's your relationship with her?
I'm her fiancé.
No kidding?
Hmm...
You two sure are fascinating.
With your considerable magic,
if you were to marry her...
You could change the world as we know it.
Not that we plan on doing so.
Aren't you witches the same,
always staying out of the public eye?
Nothing fun comes from public attention.
I must be going now,
to attend to some business.
We'll meet again, if fate so dictates.
The story is that Hubert was killed in combat.
So is Lucrezia the one who killed him?
Well, I can't blame her.
It seems that sixty years ago,
Lucrezia entered the Mirror of Oblivion
of her own will to try and destroy it.
Unable to do so, she put up
a barrier in a nearby cave,
sealing away both the mirror and herself.
When you put that together with what you heard,
that'd mean Valt broke that barrier
and gave Hubert the mirror.
Why was Senn inside?
When the barrier was broken,
her magic leaked out into the air.
That aroused his suspicions, and he was
sealed away when he went to check it out.
I see now.
Well, looks like it all
turned out well for you.
You hesitated to kill her because
that spirit was friendly with her.
By neutralizing Magdalsia's
troops without harming them,
your strange powers terrorized many.
As a result, the magic empire of Tuldarr
has spread as a name to be feared.
Isn't that exactly what you wanted?
I'm feeling a little bit tired now.
Stop acting all on your own already.
You really need to have
a little more trust in me.
I didn't want to cause you any trouble.
If you come off as a danger,
it'll be harder to get married.
Couldn't you just use your powers as
the owner of Akashia to abduct me?
Lock me up in the castle,
and it'd be the same as if we got married.
You need to rethink some things
if you consider that the same.
Imprisoning royalty was pretty
common back in the Dark Age.
How can I make it clear
that times have changed?
Go back and learn the basics.
You're calling off our engagement?
No!
Still, I have to wonder
what Valt is playing at.
Did he mention anything else
that piqued your interest?
Not at all.
Then forget I asked.
Just so you know, you're the only woman for me.
Where'd that come from?
I know that.
Oh, if something's worrying you,
we can start over and go back to basics.
Seriously, stop.
I'm...
the one who made you come to this era.
I'll definitely make you happy.
I'm plenty happy already.
You made sure to keep the promise
you made when I was a child.
Things are about to get busy again.
Your abdication, then Legis's
coronation, and two days after that...
Our wedding ceremony.
It'd be nice to be free
of setbacks from now on.
I, Legis Dys Kacoratis Gul Tuldarr,
hereby ascend the throne
as the forty-fourth king of Tuldarr.
Tuldarr was founded in the Dark Age
to protect the rights and lives of mages,
and mutual support among mages...
Oh, so you really did come.
Valt.
It happened long ago.
There once stood here an azure tower.
For those who overcame the trials
of the tower and made it to the very top,
it was said that the witch who lived
there would grant a wish.
Though that tower no longer exists,
be it in the past or future.
Are you saying I was that witch?
Yes.
The fifth witch, said to be the strongest:
the Witch of the Azure Moon.
She was even stronger
and crueler than you are now.
Does that surprise you?
A little.
Although I figured that might be the case.
When I learned you had failed to
become a witch for the very first time,
and had fallen into a magic slumber...
I was overjoyed.
Come.
It's about time we bring this to an end.
Let us go and retrieve
the other half of Eleterria.
I won't be doing any such thing.
Please return that at once.
You will.
You'll be raring to go.
What are you...
You can't be serious!
What I'm taking as hostage is this very nation.
Once this magic circle activates,
it will bring forth an inferno.
And as it consumes
all the lives within its reach,
those lives will act as a catalyst to summon
magical power, annihilating this nation.
Fail to cooperate, and Tuldarr will be no more.
Where did you learn to create this spell?
Among the many forbidden curses to summon
magical power with souls as the catalyst,
this one...
it's the same curse used four hundred
years ago, unrecorded in history.
Our kind transcribes knowledge
and passes it down.
Go back far enough, and the man you
considered a brother was one of them.
That's all there is to it.
What a sick joke.
Are you saying you and your ilk have
lurked in the shadows of all history?
Oh, no.
Our family of Time-Readers is
not as influential as you'd believe.
Every generation has but one family head.
Until the previous head dies,
the powers of the successor do not awaken.
As for the other heads, past and future, the
only knowledge I have is all of their names.
Just so you understand,
I wasn't the one who cast this spell.
If you kill me, the caster
will activate the spell.
You will by no means leave Tuldarr to die,
which is precisely
why I chose Tuldarr as my target.
But that's not my only reason.
This country is one that
should never have existed.
What?
You see, Tuldarr was destroyed
the moment your stomach was torn open.
No way...
You're wrong.
I mean, didn't I manage to suppress
the magical power back then?
Yes.
However, the magical power
summoned by sacrificing Lanak
and that summoned by sacrificing you
were orders of magnitude apart.
You were unable to fully
contain all that magic,
and what was leftover destroyed Tuldarr,
before spraying across the mainland.
The true form of this age,
for most of Tuldarr territory, was a wasteland
ravaged by that forbidden curse.
You're lying...
That can't be...
The world mends itself to minimize
the effects of the changes from Eleterria.
But the consequences of changing the fate
of an entire country were great indeed.
I feel no guilt in taking
Tuldarr as my hostage,
since it never should have existed at all.
What about you, though?
Because Tuldarr survived, a great number
of Cezar citizens were made to suffer instead.
Do you feel no remorse at all?
If Tuldarr had been destroyed
as it should have been,
Cezar would not be like this now.
You mean to say that their fate was the price
we paid for Tuldarr's prosperity?
And that at the root of it all is Oscar...
and me?
Even if what you say is true,
I won't let you claim that you are free of sin.
The one who summoned the evil god in Cezar,
as well as the one who aims
to destroy Tuldarr now,
is none other than you.
That's true.
We are both sinners.
Both of us perpetually betraying this world.
The choice to keep one
means abandoning another.
We are all made to choose without end.
Challenged to do so without end.
And if what results...
Is our current reality...
I will protect my nation.
There is no doubt that Tuldarr exists now.
Even if it came about by altering history,
I will not choose to abandon
the country before my eyes.
I thought that might be your decision.
If you wish to save your country,
you will listen to my demands.
Will I find Eleterria in Tuldarr's treasury?
What do you plan to do
after obtaining them both?
One should be enough
if you want to change the past.
I'm well aware.
But what I'm after is to change the future.
Traveling to the future?
You are the most powerful mage in history.
Not long ago, you destroyed
an outsiders' artifact, the Mirror of Oblivion.
But since you're no longer a witch,
you are inferior to your original self.
As such, I took it upon myself
to test your powers.
As luck would have it, you chose
to absorb Simila's incarnation.
The destruction of Eleterria.
That's what I'm after.
All of your actions up until now...
They were all for this moment?
~ Death of the Nameless Story ~